<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>User Manual on PhotonLoop User Manual</title><link>/userguide.html</link><description>Recent content in User Manual on PhotonLoop User Manual</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/userguide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Safety Instructions</title><link>/userguide/safety.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/userguide/safety.html</guid><description>Read carefully the information in this manual before installing and using the product. The producer is not responsible for damages and injury, which can occur due to false handling of the product and ignoring the safety instructions. All warranty will be spoiled in this case.
The tools provided by Dynamic Optics are intended to be used for wavefront sensing and compensation tasks. Please comply with the requirements for the proper use of this product.</description></item><item><title>Installation</title><link>/userguide/installation.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/userguide/installation.html</guid><description>Package Contents The devices supplied by Dynamic Optics for a standard adaptive optical system should include:
Item Description
PhotonLoop Dongle key.
This key will permit you to run PhotonLoop.
USB Memory Stick
Each product from Dynamic Optics is delivered with a USB key containing the principal information (manuals and datasheet, etc..) regarding the purchased products.</description></item><item><title>Optical Setup</title><link>/userguide/ao-setup.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/userguide/ao-setup.html</guid><description>A typical setup for adaptive optics includes a deformable optical element that could be a lens or a mirror connected to a controller, the feedback for the controller is provided by the wavefront sensor. In this configuration the AO system is working in closed loop. If the measurements of the wavefront is not used as a control feedback, the system is working in open loop. In the standard setup we offer a deformable lens or mirror controlled by a controller and a Shack-Hartmann wavefront sensor (SHWFS) for the feedback.</description></item><item><title>Wavefront Measurement</title><link>/userguide/wavefront-measurement.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/userguide/wavefront-measurement.html</guid><description>An accurate wavefront measurement is very important for metrology applications and for appropriate adaptive optics operation. Errors in measurements setting might causes system instability and if the relative errors are very high the system may not work.
Create measure grid and adjust camera settings All the buttons and options for these steps are in the following toolbox that you can find in the viewfinder widget.
To display spots and measurements grid click on and buttons respectively.</description></item><item><title>Aberration Correction</title><link>/userguide/compensation.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/userguide/compensation.html</guid><description>Calibration of the AO system After conjugation and definition of the grid it is possible to perform the calibration of the system. Not that the calibration and also AO functions need an accurate measurement of the wavefront. Before start be familiar with the wavefront measurement. Go in the Calibration Tab and you will find all the calibrations parameters. These parameters can be divided in three main blocks, as shown in the next figure.</description></item><item><title>TCP-IP</title><link>/userguide/tcpip.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/userguide/tcpip.html</guid><description>System Requirements PhotonLoop 1.5.8.3 (or later)
Matlab communication libraries
Files In the Folder TCP_IP_PhotonLoop1.5.8.3:
PhotonLoopCommunication.dll C comunication library
PhotonLoopCommunication_lib.m MATLAB comunication library
PhotonLoopCommunication_interface.m MATLAB and lib.thunk interface
PhotonLoopCommunication_thunk_pcwin64.dll MATLAB and C library interface
TCPIPExample.m MATLAB example
Here it is described the step by step procedure to modify the actuators of a deformable mirror with TCP-IP protocol without measuring or monitoring the wavefront in PhotonLoop.</description></item><item><title>Plugins</title><link>/userguide/plugins.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/userguide/plugins.html</guid><description>The sensor, WFC and compensator sections of PhotonLoop are populated by plugins. Upon starting, PhotonLoop scans the plugin inside the plugin folder /plugins/ located at the root of the PhotonLoop installation directory.
If a plugin is not listed then it is likely that some of its dependencies are not met. Be sure to install the appropriate drivers before starting PhotonLoop.
Sensor Plugins Select the sensor driver from within the sensor settings widget.</description></item></channel></rss>